Guide to the Margaret Meier Collection of Extreme Right Ephemeral Materials, 1930-1980
Department of Special Collections
- Series 3. Newspapers
  - The Valley Citizen,1963 June - 1963 Dec (Box 6, Folder 20)
    4 issues + duplicates
  - The Wanderer1965 Sept (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - The Weekly People1963 July (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Freedom Press (Santa Barbara, CA)1961 Aug 1967 Nov (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Independent American1961 June - 1969 Jan (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1960s Underground Press: Underground Digest, Article on Underground Editor Paul Krasner Canadian Free Press, The Flash, LA Free Press, LA Underground, Open Market/Open City, Oracle, The Paper1930s - 1960s (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 1930s-1940s Newspapers: Soviet Worker Today, Daily Worker, New Masses, Daily People's World1930s - 1940s (Box 9, Folder 2)